lilypie.com 2018-10-09

# Lilypie - Privacy Policy

**OVERVIEW**

In this Privacy Policy, "us", "we" or "our" means Lilypie.com (ABN 72 866 880 115). Lilypie.com allows you to receive newsletters, send feedback and use the Lilypie tickers. We use the information that we collect about you to create a more personalized online experience. This is just a brief overview, so please read on for more details about our Privacy Policy. This Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others. 

Please contact us if you have any questions. 

This Privacy Policy will explain the following regarding use of our site: 

  1. **What information does Lilypie.com collect from you?**

Lilypie.com collects two types of information about its visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you register a Lilypie account, or send us feedback. For example, this information might include your name, and e-mail address. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. For example, this information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop.

TOP
  2. **Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide Lilypie.com's visitors with requested services. 

We review the actions of the Lilypie.com visitors on an aggregate basis to determine customers' preferences. Lilypie.com also does research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and pages viewed based on the information provided to us from our server log files and the HTTP headers. We receive reports from our ad server, third party ad servers, content servers, or a web site analysis agent that tells us how many ads were presented and clicked upon or what content was served or viewed. 

We gather information in the following ways: 

    1. **Lilypie account**

If you decide to create a 'My Lilypie' account through our site we will collect and use your email address and password. This information is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy except as explained here.

    2. **Newsletter**

If you sign up for the free newsletter, we will store your email and send you newsletters periodically to let you know what is new on the site.

    3. **Contact Information**

If you contact Lilypie.com through the contact page (https://lilypie.com/contact.php), by e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. If you contact us through our contact page (https://lilypie.com/contact.php) we will gather information about your browser, IP and from your Lilypie cookies in order to help you with any problems. If you contact us through the Lilypie [Contact Developer](https://apps.facebook.com/lilypie/contactFB.php) link on Facebook (https://apps.facebook.com/lilypie/contactFB.php), we will also gather your numeric Facebook ID in order to check on the status of your tickers.

    4. **Ticker Information**

When you create or edit a ticker we store all the information you entered, your timezone, a randomly generated ticker ID and the date in order to create the requested ticker. If you are signed in to 'My Lilypie' the ticker will also be associated with your 'My Lilypie' account. 

    5. **Cookies**

Cookies are an industry standard and most major web sites use them. A cookie is a small text file that a site may place on your computer. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

TOP  

  3. **Lilypie.com use of cookies.**

Lilypie.com Cookies: When you sign in to 'My Lilypie' we will store cookies on your computer to keep you signed in. If you don't select "Keep logged in" the cookie will be deleted at the end of the session. Our cookies store a randomly assigned user identification number. You will be unable to use 'My Lilypie' without your browser being set to accept cookies. We also use a cookie to store your language choice when you create a ticker.

TOP  

  4. **Google Analytics**

Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage. [More Details on Google Analytics](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245) (https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). 

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in Google's [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) (http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie or use the [opt-out service provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

TOP  

  5. **Advertisers use of cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies when serving ads on Lilypie.com. You may opt out of the use of these cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) (https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

TOP  

  6. **With whom do we share your information?**

Other Parties: We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others without your consent. We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information. We may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property, and safety of Lilypie.com, our users, or others. 

Services Provided on Our Site: Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, without your consent, Lilypie.com does not disclose its customers' Personally Identifiable Information.

TOP  

  7. **What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?**

Newsletter: You may "opt-out," or unsubscribe from our newsletter by following the unsubscribe instructions in any newsletter e-mail you receive from us. After doing so, Lilypie.com users will not receive future newsletter emails 

My Lilypie: You may cancel your 'My Lilypie' account by contacting us through the Contact page (https://lilypie.com/contact.php) and requesting that your account be closed. Before your account is closed, you can request any tickers associated with your 'My Lilypie' account be deleted.

TOP  

  8. **Security**

Your Information is stored on Lilypie.com's server located in the United States. We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

TOP  

  9. **Contacting Lilypie.com about privacy questions or concerns**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please Contact us

TOP  

  10. **Privacy Policy changes**

If Lilypie.com makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.

TOP
